Hello hello and welcome you all how can we see
30 frustrations in Hollywood so
in this video we are going to talk about another interesting company
which is
from the general insurance sector for companies like
Reliance General Insurance Company in the country
and largest private sector
general insurance company in the country so let us
understand the meaning of this word general insurance. In such a case,
in the case of life insurance company, companies can cover any percentage of
loss and loss,
meaning if the person dies, then
some claim is provided to his beneficiary. The
company was a life insurance company and general insurance
company is its complete opposite
but general insurance company does
not cover any life related matter.
First of all, general insurance is also known as non-life
insurance. There are several
categories of general insurance companies like
health insurance, motor insurance,
travel insurance, home fire insurance
and marine crop insurance and if we
talk about India's life insurance market, then India's general life insurance
market has seen a lot of
infiltrators globally and if we look
at the premium  A percentage of GDP see
premium simply means any person who receives insurance pays
any amount to the company in exchange for insurance, that is
called premium, so free enjoy
percentage and GDP if we check USA then
this point one South Korea 4.5
South Africa Tour 60 ki 2.1 Chanel 2101
Szechwan there is no side effect for us it is a matter
of happiness for us it is a good thing
because it shows that there is a
good follow up in the market side room for hair growth
and if we talk about premium per capita then
it is vote for them in five years drops
of United States and 150 South Korea has
170 ye ki 937 2018 Chanel and Jasmine
uses of India and one more interesting
thing from Divya Wikipedia
sitting motor vehicles per thousand people are responsible
top-10 countries including St.
Mary New Zealand United States Ireland
Finland Australia-New Zealand Extra
so first company is first to support is on the
country in which  100 263 Vacation Diet
Eight No in the stomach 734 in Australia
716 in Switzerland you know
where we will hit in this list our
India ranks
at number 137 in this list which is a list of only 108 countries
India has only
28th thousand people on Phalsund so this further
shows how much
growth potential is there in the industry right now as the
income size of Indian consumers will increase then look
everyone's family is trim so
as the consumers of the company its
family size will decrease then definitely
we will see demand in these automobile sector
and demand in the alternative sector simply
means if they do it then they will have to get insurance
why why not brother now
even the challan is not less than 5 to 10 thousand so
simply the more the demand in the automobile industry will
increase the more
demand will be seen in the insurance sector as well
Its strong rotation
industry. If we talk about the overall industry, there
is a good growth potential in the industry. As you have seen, right now
our solution is only one. We want to see which company can
grow well along with the industry within the industry. So, we are going to
talk about this company
whose name is ICICI Lombard
General Insurance Company Limited. ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company The
country internet GDPI related any
skimming no feedback premium income which
you can understand right now as the revenue of the general insurance company.
Generations company's revenue
GDP means project premium income is the
largest company in the private sector.
If we look at this, it has a double
final product portfolio, which means the company provides a
lot of types of insurance policies
including health, motor, fire, fire, rent,
marine, engineering and
liability insurance agency. In the
string Ramesh, if we talk about 2021 and 2021 means
quarter to quarter and the
oil which is being seen is the product mix. MP3 percent has
come from motor, body, motor and damage, 20%
from motor third party, 5% from health,
travel and personal accident.  22% Marine
which is three percent and anger has been zero percent
and ten percent is ideal, anger is zero
percent means look at it earlier, funny 10 crore
was 70% which the company has brought to zero by the time it reaches zero, it has
brought it to zero because
from this industry, a segment C company had seen a
lot of falls, the claims review was
quite high, low fresh was quite high, this
company has decided to consolidate from this segment
which is a positive sign and the
company is focusing only on its margin business, on the
other hand, its product mix
also seems that the company does not have much support
in any particular segment,
next important thing is the
company's
tuition network is quite good, there are 250 plus
offices, plus individual agents, there are
840 plus virtual offices, this company's
distribution channels are direct sales
division, agents are patented like banks, PAN
brokers and digital zoom, here this company provides police to its
individual cooperative and government customers, the
third most
important thing  The promoters of the company and the
management of the company
are the promoters of Vivo company. ICICI Bank Limited, which is
the largest private sector bank, is a
very important positive factor
for us, for the company and for the ward. And if
we talk a little about the fans of the company, then the
revenue in the financial year 2016 was
back to 13430 million rupees, which has increased to 13430 million rupees till the financial year 2016. The
profit after tax has also improved from 5.07 to 11.30,
which is 1520 in the last three to
four years. A
reminder of this issue is another important
factor in the insurance
industry, combined growth, which has improved by
1065 to 2051 in function 16. And
if we look at it now, according to the successful Twenty20,
this 9998 fans have improved.
Combined are  Simply means loss ratio plus
expense ratio means the loss ratio means the
percentage of net
cream given by the company means the amount of Chanakya
premium the company has paid as compared to the amount of preventive Arun the company has paid,
that loss ratio plus
how much the company has spent on operating expenses,
such percentage of the net premium as
described in the company,
how many expenses have been incurred in comparison to the amount the
company has added, then by adding
both of them the combined
pressure is formed, if the loss point rates are higher
then it is not a positive sign at all, it
means that the
company has incurred more expenses than what the company has added,
after giving operating expenses plus claims,
this is a positive sign which means
that if at the time of 98% of the body of
any such company, if the
combined savings are 100%, then still they are profitable, this simply
means that the company has  The
company has also
got good returns from its investments, that is why the company
is not profitable and the return and average
equity fund share of 9020 is 1.3 percent which has been the
highest-ever till 24.98 till 2020. Solvency is an
important
factor in the insurance industry.
Solvency issues mean what is the capacity
of any insurance company to provide balance,
which according to IAI i.e.
Insurance Regulatory and Development
Authority of India, should be 1.5 percent i.e.
one fifty percent, it should be 1.5
which is an addition to Lambda, in this one is
Bluetooth of furniture and security and now
brother follow strictly according to
point 17-A, it was zero, it has increased to 2.5 percent,
so this also
shows the strong furniture position of the company, so
if we look a little bit at Kumbh Tekar
according to screen.in, then its
computers look, acidity is also like this,
life is given, this is ICICI Prudential
Life  There is also General
Insurance, there is also New India Assurance,
none of these is its direct
competitor
except New India Assurance because
HDFC is Life Insurance Company, instead of
Life Insurance, there is ICICI Prudential. If there is
Life Insurance, then we
will compare it only with New India
Assurance, which is a government owned company. We have a
look at PF TV and it is later
trailed. New India Assurance's
operating profit margin at 11pm is ICICI
Lombard's 14.77, case of New India
Assurance support 547, debt to equity
ratio 0.07, fake jewellery debt is
100, debt free absolutely.
Promoter holding is 51189 persons. Promoter holding is
as told, the promoters are ICICI
Bank Limited, 21.9 percent. This ratio is quite good.
This ratio is maintained by ICICI Bank.
This shows that the promoters have a lot of
confidence in the growth of the industry and the growth of the company. Again, the most
positive is the holding of factory cleaning.  That 551
Sure Dog in how usefully they are
acquiring their holdings, so
this is an important factor, see let's come to the topic no
nonsense conclusion, due to which consumer's
corporation is increasing, people are
aware about function protection and according to the world
average,
our insurance sector is quite printed, whereas in my
opinion the industry has a lot of
growth potential and ICICI
Lombard is a desi company, its promoters'
track record has been very good,
they have good experience, the
company has a diversified product portfolio and provides all
types of insurance policies
and the distribution network of the company is
strong, so all these things
show that Lombard
is in a very good position and has the ability to grab support from him, in
this way as the
company increases with care, as the company
starts, then the share price will also definitely
follow, so that's all in this video, to
get more such videos,
subscribe to the channel and hit the bell icon
and if you liked the
video,  Like and next time,
please suggest us in the comment section which company's English we should do.
Thank you very much for watching the video.